本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
我不想再见到你们中任何一个
I don't want to see either one of you ever again.
能照办吗
Do we have a deal or not?
我们照办就是了
Yeah, we got a deal.
跟着他
I'm going after him.
我们该收手了
We're done.
我们才刚刚开始呢
We're just getting started.
珍妮
Jenny!
我们得谈谈你拘捕塔林的问题
We need to talk about you having Tarin arrested.
我知道塔林是你的朋友
I know you consider Tarin a friend.
我们不止是朋友
We are more than friends.
我们相爱了
We're in love.
你一直都背着我在和这个男人...
You've been carrying on with this man...
交往吗
behind my back?
这些都是什么人  萨米尔
Who are these men, Samir?
都是我招募的手下
These are men I have recruited.
我们无法把浓缩铀棒运出这个国家
We can't get the rods out of the country,
那只好做成核弹了
so let's use them as a radiological bomb.
要给美国佬点颜色看看
Then we'll show the Americans how strong we are.
到这边来
Over here!
有人在追杀我
There are people chasing me.
你们要找的浓缩铀棒就在他们手里
They have the rods you are looking for.
我还以为在你手里
I thought you had the rods.
他们出尔反尔
They turned against me.
快来救我出去
Just get me out of here.
我们会来救你的  哈桑先生
We'll get you out, Mr. Hassan.
如果事情搞得一发不可收拾
When things get this colossally screwed up
总得有个替罪羊
people look for someone to blame.
那你怎么想的
So what have you got in mind?
蕾妮·沃克  杀了能为我们提供主要线索的人
Renee Walker-- she killed one of our main leads.
你是叫我起诉一个自愿为祖国
You're talking about a woman who put her life on the line
出生入死的的女人吗
when she didn't have to.
总得有人来背这个黑锅吧  布赖恩
Well, someone has to pay for this, Brian.
我从司法部派了个人来  克蕾丝丁·史密斯
I'm sending someone over from Justice-- Kristin Smith.
一切由她来处理
She'll take care of everything.
他们在陷害你  一句话也别说
They're setting you up-- don't say another word.
审讯结束了  我们离开这里
This is over. We're leaving now.
举起手来
Hands in the air.
-你愿意营救法哈德吗  -对
- You offering to bring in Farhad? - Yes.
条件是你撤销对蕾妮·沃克的刑事调查
If you drop the criminal investigation against Renee Walker.
如果我们要达成协议  杰克
If we do this, Jack,
这就不仅是为一次救援行动了
it's not for one rescue operation,
而是得把整件事都圆满了结
it's till this whole thing is over and done.
以下事件发生于凌晨一点至两点间
The following takes place between 1:00 A.M. and 2:00 A.M.
我们马上要把他押送到大使馆
We're about to transport him to the embassy.
你只有两分钟时间
You have two minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
巴希尔  让他们单独待会儿
Bashir, clear the room.
塔林  他们伤害你了吗
Tarin, did they hurt you?
暂时还没
Not yet.
不过到了大使馆就不好说了
They won't until they get me to our embassy.
我试着和我父亲理论
I tried to reason with my father,
但他充耳不闻
but he wouldn't listen.
他认为你和他弟弟有牵连
He thinks you're involved in the conspiracy with his brother.
即便他得知我们相爱的事  他还是不信你
Even after I told him about us, he doesn't trust you.
你告诉了他我们相爱的事
You told him about us?
我还指望他能回心转意
I hoped it would change his mind.
但事与愿违  情况变得更糟了
But if anything, it's made things worse between us.
近几步说话
Come closer.
听我说  凯拉
Listen to me, Kayla,
我有一个办法能脱身
there is a way out of this.
我手下还有几个人对我忠心耿耿
There are a few men still loyal to me--
巴希尔就是其中之一
Bashir is one of them.
他答应助我脱逃
He's agreed to help me escape.
一有机会  巴希尔就会悄悄把手铐钥匙塞给我
As soon as he's able, Bashir will slip me a handcuff key,
他还在车里为我藏了一把枪
and he's placed a gun in the car for me to find.
不会有人受伤吧
You won't hurt anyone?
枪是万不得已的选择
The gun is so I won't have to.
我一旦脱身  我有藏身之地
Once I'm free, I have a place to stay
直到得到美国政府的政治庇护
until the Americans grant me asylum.
凯拉  我想让你和我一起走
Kayla... I want you to come with me.
来西奥多酒店与我会合
Meet me at the Teodore Hotel.
答应我你一定会来
Promise me you'll come.
塔林  得走了
Tarin, we need to go.
科尔  他死了
Cole, he's dead!
走吧
Just go.
什么
What?
你走吧
Just go.
没人会知道你与此事有关
Nobody knows you had anything to do with this.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我是谁  我做过些什么
I lied about everything.
我满嘴谎言
Who I am, what I've done.
我会报警的
I'll call the police.
一切后果都是我应得的下场
I deserve to take the blame for this.
事已至此
What's done is done.
我们把这里清理干净
We're cleaning this up,
没人会知道发生了什么
and no one's ever gonna know what happened.
我不想让你趟这滩浑水
I don't want you involved.
我已经泥足深陷了
I'm already involved.
我们把他的车牌处理掉  这样就不会被查到
We're gonna strip down his van so it can't be I.D.'d.
把尸体丢弃在沼泽地里
We'll dump the bodies in the swamp.
他们是人渣  丹娜  没人会想念他们
They're scum, Dana, and no one's gonna miss 'em.
你想下半辈子都待监狱里吗
You want to go to prison for the rest of your life?
就为了这两个人渣
For them?!
把车启动起来
Get started on the van.
我去把另外一具尸体搬过来
I'll go get the other one.
黑斯廷斯先生  总统在线上
Mr. Hastings, the president's on the line.
谢谢  我是黑斯廷斯
Thank you. This is Hastings.
黑斯廷斯先生  我和罗伯特·维斯在一起
Mr. Hastings, I'm here with Rob Weiss.
你有紧急情况要汇报吗
I was told you have urgent news.
我们接到一个来自法哈德·哈桑的电话
We received a call from Farhad Hassan.
是的  我们怀疑他正试图
Yes. As we suspected, he was trying
把浓缩铀棒运出美国
to smuggle the nuclear rods out of the country.
和他一伙的人对他起了异心
The people he's working with have turned against him.
-接着说  -法哈德认为
- What do we know? - Well, Farhad believes
他们打算把浓缩铀棒改造成核弹
they want to use the rods to construct a dirty bomb
而且就打算在纽约引爆
and set it off somewhere here in New York City.
他们为什么要这么做
Why would they do this?
在哈桑总统和反恐组的双重压力之下
Between Hassan's crackdowns and CTU,
他们已经走投无路了
we've backed them into a corner.
他们打算狗急跳墙了
This is their response.
你相信法哈德说的吗
Do you believe him?
我信
Yes, I do.
法哈德打算自首
Farhad is turning himself in.
他答应协助我们阻止这次恐怖袭击
He's agreed to help us prevent this attack.
法哈德现在在哪
Where is Farhad now?
在一个仓库里
He's in a warehouse
就在郊区接近森林山一带
just outside the city near Forest Hills.
我已指派杰克·鲍尔前去营救他了
I've enlisted Jack Bauer to lock him down.
总统阁下
Now, Madam President,
现在已经确认背叛法哈德的那伙人
the men who turned against Farhad
就是伊斯兰共和国的间谍
are covert assets for the I.R.K.
如果我们能拿到伊斯兰共和国的情报人员文件
Now, if we can get access to the I.R.K. intelligence files,
那法哈德也许能帮助我们指认这些人
Farhad may be able to help us I.D. these men.
那样的话  我们要追踪他们就容易多了
It will put us that much closer to tracking them down.
那些文件是哈桑总统情报活动的命脉
Those files are the lifeblood of Hassan's intelligence operation--
他绝对不会交出来
he'll never hand them over.
尤其在他目前这种心理状态下
Especially in his current frame of mind.
他都已经开始走极端了
Hell, the man's gone off the deep end.
也许他弟弟的消息能让他不再那么极端
Well, maybe this will pull him out of it.
告诉哈桑  我们已经找到他的弟弟了
Tell Hassan we have found his brother
我需要立即和他谈谈
and I need to speak to him immediately.
联系国土安全局的蒂姆·伍兹
And contact Tim Woods at Homeland.
让他整理出一份简报
Have him put together a briefing.
天佑吾民  但要是袭击还是发生了
I need to know exactly what we're facing
我要确切知道我们的处境
if, God forbid, this attack happens.
谢谢  黑斯廷斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Hastings.
我马上去会议室
I'll be in the counsel chamber.
好的  总统阁下
Yes, Madam President.
维斯先生
Mr. Weiss.
什么事
Yeah?
你说吧
Yeah. What is it?
我想让你知道我已经决定
I want to let you know that I've decided
取消对蕾妮·沃克的指控了
not to pursue charges against Renee Walker.
什么
What?
为什么  我不是告诉过你...
Why not? I told you...
比起让蕾妮·沃克背黑锅
We have a lot more to worry about
我们现在还有更重要的事操心
right now than blaming Walker.
若非她杀了能为我们提供宝贵线索的人
Walker murdered a valuable lead
我们或许早就找到浓缩铀棒了
that might have gotten us to those nuclear rods.
你没听懂我说的
You're not hearing me.
我们现在有新线索了  法哈德·哈桑
We have a new lead now-- Farhad Hassan--
我正在追查此线索
and that is what I am pursuing.
你如果想撤我的职  悉听尊便
You want to replace me as head of CTU, be my guest.
如果不是的话
But until you do,
那就别挡道
stay the hell out of my way.
-黑斯廷斯  你正在犯... -杰克一到
- Hastings, you're making... - I'll let you know
法哈德那  我会通知你的
when Bauer reaches Farhad.
好了  法哈德的方位已被锁定
Okay, Farhad Hassan is located
就在仓库的东北角
on the northeast corner of the warehouse.
我们必须行动迅速  因为他身上有伤
We're gonna have to move fast, because he's injured.
金  林奇  你们从南面包抄
King, Lynch, you're gonna go in from the south.
欧文和我掩护你们的侧翼
Owen and I will cover your flank.
-明白  -我们一救出他
- Understood. - As soon as we've got him locked down,
就要马上开始审讯
we're gonna initiate our interrogation.
反恐组会上传嫌犯的资料
CTU's gonna upload files on probable suspects--
我希望电脑能尽快接收
I need that available and on a computer as soon as possible.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
鲍尔先生  我们接到从反恐组转接来的电话
Mr. Bauer, we're getting a call routed through CTU.
是法哈德·哈桑
It's Farhad Hassan.
打开免提
Put it on speaker.
我是杰克·鲍尔  请讲
This is Jack Bauer. Go ahead.
你们还有多久到
How close are you?
十分钟吧  你还好吗
Ten minutes out. Are you okay?
有人来了
There's someone here.
他们很接近我了
They're close.
他们在找我
They're looking for me.
求你了  快点
Please... hurry.
总统阁下
Madam President.
有人告诉我您已经找到我弟弟了
I'm told you have my brother.
请坐
Please.
他给反恐组打了电话
He called CTU
并且自首了
and surrendered himself.
我不明白
I don't understand.
和法哈德一伙的那帮人背叛了他
The men that Farhad was working with turned against him,
现在浓缩铀棒在他们手里
and they have taken the nuclear rods.
法哈德认为他们打算改造成一枚核弹
Now, he believes that they intend to construct a dirty bomb
并在纽约引爆它
to attack this city.
很显然  这伙人就是贵国派来美国
Now, apparently, these men are members of
从事秘密情报活动的间谍
your covert intelligence operations here in the United States.
这难以信服
I find that hard to believe.
您弟弟没理由撒谎
Well, your brother has no reason to lie.
他选择了自首  就是选择了死刑
By turning himself in, he's facing the death penalty.
所以我们认为他说的是实话
We have to assume he's telling the truth.
我需要您把您派来我国的
I need for you to give us intelligence files
所有间谍的文件都交给我们
for every asset you have in this country
这样法哈德就能指认这些恐怖份子
so Farhad can identify these terrorists.
总统阁下  我给了您很大的回旋余地
Mr. President, I have given you a great deal of latitude
来让您处理国内的局势
to sort out your domestic situation,
现在我的国家安全受到了威胁
and now there is a threat to my homeland,
而我需要您的配合
and I need your cooperation.
我建议您把法哈德交给我处置
I suggest you turn Farhad over to me
让我的人来审问他
and let my people question him.
我们会找出您要的答案
We'll get the answers you need.
没那么多时间了
There's no time for that.
此刻  反恐组小队已前去营救法哈德了
There's a CTU team moving on Farhad as we speak.
他们要就地审问他
They need to question him on site.
我需要这些文件
I need the files.
您的要求会对我国的安全造成严重危害
What you're asking is a serious breach of our security.
这个我很清楚
I understand that.
但我也请您明白
But you need to understand
如果核袭击一旦发生
that if this radiological attack takes place,
我将不得不发动反击
I will be forced to retaliate.
您是说会进攻我的国家
You would attack... my country?
我将别无选择
I will have no choice.
我需要那些文件
I need those files...
而且现在就要
and I need them now.
我会通知我的代理安全主管
I'll call my acting head of security.
几分钟内您就会拿到文件
You'll get the files in a few minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
翻译：X-Ray     LIIT     罗玉凤     wdjmhs     时间轴：何何
■
时间轴：佐佐   钉子     校对：何何   我是无辜的  罗玉凤  Nil
后期：冰河       监制：何何
■
我想告诉你  塔林
I want you to know, Tarin,
我不相信你会叛国
that I don't believe you are guilty of treason.
但我别无选择  只能服从命令
But I have no choice but to follow orders.
你不用解释  我了解   纳比尔
You don't have to explain yourself, Nabeel.
换我也会这么做的
I would do the same thing in your position.
我不会记恨你
I don't hold any of this against you.
不管我出了什么事
Whatever happens to me,
你都不必责怪自己
you must not blame yourself.
永远不要忘记
Never forget that.
我感激不尽
I appreciate that.
-别动  -你要干什么
- Don't move.  - What are you doing?
纳比尔  交出你的武器
Nabeel, give me your weapon now.
慢慢地  用两个手指拿出来
Slowly, two fingers.
快点
Come on.
司机  把车停在这
Driver, pull over here.
解开安全带
Remove your seat belts.
你们俩都把双手放在脑后
Put your hands on your head, both of you.
下车
Get out of the car now.
别动
Don't move.
把车钥匙给我
Give me the keys.
-把手放下来  -塔林  别这样做
- Put your hands down.  - Tarin, don't do this.
你这样只会让事情变得更糟
You'll only make things worse for yourself.
你清楚在大使馆他们会把我怎么样
You know what they'll do to me at our embassy.
没有比那更糟的了
It can't be any worse.
是哈桑总统
It's President Hassan.
把电话给我
Give it to me.
快点
Come on!
走吧  到后面去
Let's go. In the back.
打开后备箱
Open it up.
拿出手铐  把自己铐上
Take out your cuffs. Lock yourselves down.
纳比尔没接电话
Nabeel isn't answering.
他在哪
Where is he?
正押送塔林去大使馆
Transporting Tarin to the embassy.
继续打手机联系他
Keep trying to reach him on his mobile.
如果他还不接
If he doesn't answer,
派一支安保小队去追踪他
send a security team to track him.
遵命  总统阁下
Yes, sir.
联系艾尔·贾尼斯上校
And contact Colonel Al Jhanis.
告诉他以我的名义
Tell him on my authority
提供反恐组所需要的文件
to give CTU access to the files they requested.
遵命  总统阁下
Yes, sir.
是我  你在哪
It's me. Where are you?
我正要离开联合国大楼
I'm leaving the U.N. Right now.
一切还好吗
Is everything all right?
是的  我逃出来了  在酒店等我
Yes, it worked. Meet me at the hotel.
我十分钟就到
I'll be there in ten minutes.
我爱你  凯拉
I love you, Kayla.
一会见
I'll see you soon.
请讲  黑斯廷斯先生
Go ahead, Mr. Hastings.
法哈德  你还在那吗
Farhad, are you there?
是的  我在这
Yes, yes, I'm here.
我们的外勤小队正向南面入口靠近
Our field team is approaching the south entrance.
在他们控制住现场前待在原地别动
Stay where you are until they secure the site.
他就要发现我了
He's almost on me.
我不能待在这
I can't stay here.
在他们制伏那个枪手前不要乱动
Do not move until they lock down that shooter.
你听明白我的话了吗
Do you understand me?
法哈德
Farhad?
Farhad?!
法哈德  说话
Farhad, talk to me.
他在这
Over here!
医护兵  快点  医护兵
Medic! Come on! Medic!
是他  他就是法哈德
That's him, that's Farhad.
欧文  带你的小队搜索这片区域
Owen, take your team and sweep the area.
克罗伊  我们找到了法哈德  但他中枪了
Chloe, we've got Farhad, but he's been hit.
我现在就要那些文件
I need those files immediately.
伊斯兰共和国情报部门刚刚传过来
I.R.K. Intelligence just sent them over.
很好
Good.
喂
Yes?
搞定了
It's done.
法哈德被解决掉了
Farhad is no longer a problem.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我打中他两枪  不过警察来了
I shot him twice, but the police arrived,
我只好撤了
and I had to get out of there.
你知道到哪去找我们
You know where to find us.
是的
Yes.
鲍尔先生
Mr. Bauer.
-说吧  -他腹部中了两枪  大口径子弹
- Speak to me. - We have two large caliber slugs to the abdomen.
他正严重失血  可能撑不到医院了
He's bleeding out. I don't think he's going to make it to the hospital.
不惜一切稳定住他的伤势
Do whatever you have to do to stabilize him.
我们现在就得和他谈了  快去
We need to talk to him now. Go!
我是B组
This is B team.
发现了他们的货车  但没发现浓缩铀棒
We found their truck, but there's no sign of the rods.
文件上传完毕立即通知我
Let me know as soon as these files are uploaded.
哈桑先生  过会儿
Mr. Hassan, in a few seconds,
我会给你看几张你们国家
I'm going to show you photographs of covert operatives
潜伏在美国的间谍的照片
working for your country within the United States.
我要你指认出那些从你这里偷走浓缩铀棒的人
I need you to identify the men who stole the nuclear rods from you.
你能帮助我们吗
Can you do that for us?
好的
Yes.
文件上传好了吗
Are those files uploaded yet?!
-就快了  -再快点
- Almost. - Come on!
血压降低  心跳加剧
Blood pressure's dropping. We've got a rapid heartbeat.
出什么事了
What the hell's happening?
他要休克了  给我20毫升肾上腺素
He's going into shock. Give me 20 cc's epinephrine.
你要让他活着  听明白了吗
You keep that man alive, do you understand me?
-救活他  -别干扰我救人
- Keep him alive!  - Let me do my job!
-视频会议准备好了  总统阁下  -谢谢
- The telepresence conference is ready, Madam President. - Thank you.
很高兴见到你们  先生们
Good to see you, gentlemen.
总统阁下  反恐组的布赖恩·黑斯廷斯
Madam President, Brian Hastings at CTU
向我们汇报了最新情况
has brought us up to speed,
我们准备让您了解一下详情
and we're ready to review some specifics with you.
很好  愿闻其详
Good. I'm listening.
请您看一下屏幕
If you would refer to your monitor...
这是曼哈顿市中心的平面图
and the diagram of Midtown Manhattan.
据反恐组汇报
According to CTU,
失窃的浓缩铀棒最高可能有三百磅的爆炸当量
the stolen nuclear rods have a maximum explosive yield of 300 pounds.
并且有足够的辐射物质
That's enough radiological material
污染大约一平方英里的区域
to contaminate approximately one square mile.
如果爆炸装置在曼哈顿人口更为密集的区域引爆
If the device were detonated in a more densely populated area of Manhattan,
伤亡可能会达到数万人
we could be looking at casualties in the tens of thousands.
兰德里博士
Dr. Landry?
大多数遇难者会死于严重的辐射中毒
Most of the deaths would be from severe radiation poisoning.
剩下的受害者会死于辐射导致的并发症
The remainder of the victims would expire from radiation induced illnesses.
主要是白血病
Primarily leukemia
还有其他癌症
and other cancers.
我们还要考虑到受辐射污染的区域
We also have to consider that the affected area
将在未来大约四十年内不适于居住
would be rendered uninhabitable for approximately 40 years.
显然不能考虑全城疏散
Obviously a citywide evacuation is out of the question.
是的  有上百万人居住在这个
That's right. There are millions of people on this island
交通极为不便的岛上
with few points of egress.
全部疏散需要几天时间
It would take days to get them out.
更别说将这个消息公之于众
Not to mention that going public with this information
会引起的巨大恐慌了
would cause mass panic.
我同意  我们暂时要对公众隐瞒这个危机
I agree. We need to keep this threat from the public for now.
集中全力阻止袭击的发生
Focus our efforts on making sure that this attack never happens.
反恐组确信浓缩铀棒还在城区之外
CTU believes the nuclear rods are still outside the city,
所以他们正加强桥梁和隧道的辐射探测力度
so they're fortifying radiation detection efforts at the bridges and tunnels.
我们也在加强对重要目标的保护
We are also hardening high value targets
比如金融区  地标性建筑和地铁
such as the financial district, landmarks, subways.
联合国大楼也可能是目标之一
But we can't ignore that the U.N. may also be a target.
考虑到安全问题  我认为应该疏散整栋大楼
Given the danger, I think we should evacuate the entire building.
在一个安全地点重新召开此次会议
We can resume the conference from a safe location.
好吧  通知代表们目前的情况
All right, inform the delegates of the situation.
总统阁下
Madam president
反恐组抓获了您的弟弟
CTU has your brother in custody.
他中枪了
He's been shot.
他们正全力抢救他
They're trying to stabilize him.
说
Yes?
总统阁下  拉希姆探员打来电话
Sir, Agent Rahim is calling for you.
他说他找到了纳比尔
He says he's located Nabeel.
接通他
Put him through.
是  总统阁下
Yes, sir.
总统阁下  我们找到了纳比尔和他的司机
Mr. President, we found Nabeel and his driver
他们被锁在车的后备箱里
locked down in the back of their vehicle.
-塔林逃跑了  -什么
-Tarin has escaped.  - What?!
纳比尔要和您通话  总统阁下
Nabeel wishes to speak to you, sir.
好的  让他接电话
Yes, okay, put him on.
抱歉  总统阁下
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
塔林身上有枪
Tarin had the gun with him.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't understand how.
你是说有人协助他逃跑吗
Are you saying somebody helped him escape?
我觉得是
It would seem so.
但总统阁下
But Mr. President,
还有件事我要告诉您
there's something else you need to know.
他脱身后  我偷听到塔林在打电话
Right after he escaped, I overheard Tarin on the phone.
我想他在和您女儿通话
I believe he was speaking to your daughter.
凯拉  你确定吗
Kayla? Are you sure about this?
是的  总统阁下
Yes, sir.
听上去他要去城里的一个地方见她
It sounded like he was going to meet her somewhere in the city.
凯拉  给我回电话
Kayla, call me back.
回电话  凯拉
Call me back, Kayla.
进来
Come inside.
谢天谢地你没事
Oh, thank God, you're all right.
我联系了一位我认识的美国律师
I contacted an American lawyer I know
他是国际法方面的专家
who's an expert at international law.
他答应两个小时内见我们
He's agreed to meet us in two hours.
虽然目前情况很糟糕
This is such a terrible situation.
但我却从未如此高兴过
Yet I've never felt so happy.
我也一样
I feel the same.
鲍尔先生  我们尽力了
Mr. Bauer, we did our best.
他没撑过去
He didn't make it.
我知道你尽力了  谢谢
I know you did. Thanks.
我们搜查了整个区域  长官  没人了
We swept the area, sir. It's clear.
没有敌人和浓缩铀棒的踪迹
No hostiles. No trace of the nuclear rods.
明白
Copy that.
反恐组  我是鲍尔
CTU, this is Bauer.
法哈德死了
We lost him. Farhad's dead.
该死
Damn it.
我认为我们还有别招可用
I still think we've got another play.
对法哈德开枪的人无法确定他是否死了
Whoever shot Farhad couldn't confirm that he was killed.
我们从半路杀出来
We came up on him too fast.
他们不知道他伤得有多么严重
They don't know how badly he was wounded.
那么你有何高见  杰克
So what are you proposing, Jack?
我的意思是用法哈德作为诱饵
I'm saying that we use Farhad as dead bait.
给媒体放话说我们抓获了他
Leak it to the press that we've got him in custody,
而且他还活着
and he survived.
我们正把他送往当地一家医院
We're transporting him to a local hospital
当局会在那里对他进行审问
where authorities are going to question him.
他们不得不再次对他下手
They'll have to make a move on him.
他知道的太多了
He knows too much.
像是死马当活马医了
Sounds like a Hail Mary.
这是我们目前唯一的救命稻草了
Right now it's the only play we've got.
如果不出我所料  他们对法哈德下手
But if they make a move on Farhad, which I think they will,
我们就可以守株待兔
we'll be waiting for them.
黑斯廷斯  你说过在事情完全平息前
Mr. Hastings, you said you wanted me in
你要我全力以赴  这就是证明
till this was resolved. This is it.
我们拿到了哈桑情报人员的文件
We have Hassan's intelligence files.
我们可以用面部识别系统进行扫描和交叉比对
We can scan and cross-reference with facial recognition software.
说不定能在袭击之前找到这些恐怖分子
Maybe spot the terrorists before they attack.
好吧  杰克
All right, Jack.
这也许并不是很标准的程序
It's not exactly standard procedure
拉着个死人满城转悠
ferrying a dead man's body across the city,
不过我愿意一试
but I'm willing to give it a shot.
我们这边会安排一条前往医院的路线
We'll figure out a hospital route
同时整理好一份对媒体的声明
and put a press statement together.
你那边也做好准备
You get ready on your end.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
准备好把尸体抬上车运走
Get that body ready for transport.
欧文  把你的人集结起来
Owen, assemble your men.
-五分钟之内做简报  -是  长官
- Briefing in less than five. - Yes, sir.
空中一号已到达指定路线上空  长官
Aerial one is in position over the route, sir.
狙击手小队已报到  全部就位
Sniper teams have checked in. They're all in place.
赶快  抓紧时间
Come on, hurry up.
走
Let's go.
一切都结束了  丹娜
It's over, Dana.
我们去处理另一具尸体
Let's get the other body
在返回反恐组之前把这些处理干净
and get cleaned up before we head back to CTU.
科尔  我们之间的事怎么办
Cole, what about us?
我不知道
I don't know.
我台刚从纽约反恐组总部获悉
We have just received word from New York Counterterrorist Headquarters
卡米斯坦伊斯兰共和国总统
that Farhad Hassan-- brother of
奥马·哈桑的弟弟  法哈德·哈桑
Islamic Republic of Kamistan President Omar Hassan--
目前还活着
has been found alive.
据称法哈德·哈桑较早前曾联络过反恐组
We're told that Farhad Hassan contacted CTU
表示同意向当局自首
a short while ago and agreed to turn him over to authorities.
法哈德还活着
Farhad is alive.
什么
What?
反恐组马上做出回应
CTU responded immediately,
但当他们到达时却发现他遭到了枪击
but when they arrived, they found him shot.
声明中尚未提及他是如何受的枪伤
No word yet on how Farhad Hassan sustained these gunshot injuries,
但我们确知他将会幸存下来
but we do know that he is expected to survive,
他正在高度戒备的状态下
and he's being transported
被送往圣朱利安医院
to St. Julian's Hospital under heightened security
当局将在那里对他进行审问
where he will be questioned by authorities.
这不可能
This is impossible.
法哈德在今晚早些时候一直在逃...
Farhad Hassan has been on the run since early this evening...
我打中他两枪
I shot him twice.
但是你没有确认他死了
But you didn't make sure he was dead.
我说过了  当时没时间了
I told you I didn't have time!
我自己的烂摊子自己来收拾
I'll make this right. I'll go back.
你太招摇了
You're too conspicuous.
法哈德会受到严密保护
Farhad will be heavily protected.
但如果法哈德招供了
But if Farhad talks,
当局就会在我们改造好武器之前找到我们
the authorities could find us before we can build the weapon.
你以为我们就不知道那意味着什么吗
You think we don't know the implications?
我们派马科斯过去
We're sending Marcos.
他母亲是美国人
His mother's American.
他们不会怀疑他
They won't suspect him.
他在卡车里看守浓缩铀棒
He's in the truck with the rods.
喂
Hello?
妈妈  是我
Mom, it's me.
马科斯吗
Marcos?
嗯  听好  我不能讲太长时间
Yes. Listen, I can't talk for long.
怎么了  你还好吗
What is it? Are you okay?
我很好  妈妈
I'm fine, Mom.
我需要你为我做些事情
I need you to do something for me.
事关重大
It's very important.
好的
Okay.
什么事情
Okay. What is it?
我要你马上起床并且离开这座城市
I need you to get up right now and leave the city.
-到雪莱阿姨那里去  -雪莱阿姨那里
- Go to Aunt Shelley's. - Aunt Shelley's?!
就当为了我  好吗
Just do it for me, okay?
别问我为什么
Don't ask me why.
马上走
Leave right now.
马科斯
Marcos,
这太离谱了
this is crazy...
我不会大半夜无缘无故地离开自己家
I'm not gonna leave the apartment in the middle of the night for no reason.
并非无缘无故  只是现在还不能告诉你
There's a reason; I just can't tell you what it is right now.
求你了  妈妈  就当为了我
Please, Mom, do this for me.
你在哪
Where are you?
别为我担心
Don't worry about me.
我要是不确定你的安危我就哪也不去
Well, I'm not going anywhere unless I know you're all right.
我会去雪莱阿姨那里找你
I'll meet you at Aunt Shelley's,
到时候我会告诉你一切
and I'll explain everything.
快走  妈妈  马上
Go, Mom, now.
好吧  我这就走
Okay, I'm leaving.
我得挂了  我爱你
I have to go. I love you.
准备好了吗  哥们
Are you ready, my friend?
准备好了
Yes.
很好
Good.
是时候了
It's time.
一路上你要让他看起来像还活着
You need to keep him looking alive the entire way.
-都清楚自己的任务了吗  -是的  长官
- You're all clear on what you need to do? - Yes, sir.
-杰克  我是黑斯廷斯  -请讲
- Jack, it's Hastings. - Go ahead.
我已经跟新闻机构协调好了
We've coordinated with news outlets.
他们把法哈德被逮捕
They put out the false report of Farhad's arrest
并被送往医院接受审问的假消息发出去了
and transport to the hospital for questioning.
只等大鱼上钩了
The hook has been baited.
好的  最符合逻辑的袭击时机是
Okay. The most logical place for them
我们前往医院的途中
to attack is when we're en route.
在半路上我们的防御是最脆弱的
That's where we're gonna be our most vulnerable.
纽约警察和反恐特警已经出发了
Well, NYPD and SWAT are mobilizing now.
他们会埋伏在沿途的战略要点上
They're going to be embedded at strategic points along the way.
他们同时严密警戒圣朱利安医院
They're also securing St. Julian's Hospital.
明白  告诉支援小组
Copy that. Tell the support teams
务必要活捉这些恐怖分子
it is imperative that we take these terrorists alive.
我们通知过他们了  杰克
They've been briefed, Jack.
好的  我们出发了
Okay, we're moving out.
你们两个坐后边的车
You two take the follow van.
明白
Copy that.
你还好吗
Hey, are you all right?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
我知道你和你的手下
Look, I know you and your men
还没有太多的实战经验
have not had a lot of field experience,
而我们却让你们处理这么极端的情况
and we have put you in an extreme situation.
不过我保证  要是我们被袭击
But I promise you, if we're attacked,
整条路线都会有人提供掩护
every part of this route is covered.
我们会在那里得到大量的支援
We've got a lot of support out there.
我很好  鲍尔先生
I'm fine, Mr. Bauer.
出发吧
Let's do this.
好
Yeah.
我们一行代表准备前往麦圭尔空军基地
Our delegation is preparing to head to McGuire Air force Base.
我将在那里设置一个临时指挥中心
We'll be setting up a temporary ops center there,
从而能够掌控局势的发展
where we'll be able to monitor the situation.
那其他的代表呢
And the other delegates?
联合国安保人员会协调疏散
U.N. Security will coordinate the evacuation.
整个过程会顺利进行
Everything should go smoothly.
想喝点儿什么吗  总统阁下
Can I get you anything, Madam President?
不用  谢谢  罗伯
No, thank you, Rob.
你已经够尽职尽责了
You have done more than enough.
我非常抱歉你刚上任几个月
I'm just sorry that your first few months
就面对如此巨大的挑战
on the job have been so challenging.
这是我得到锻炼的最好机会
I wouldn't have had it any other way.
待会儿见
I'll see you in a moment.
我的一个手下告诉我
I spoke to one of my aides.
他说我弟弟... 死了
He told me my brother is... dead.
确实如此
I'm afraid so.
反恐组结束这次行动之后
When CTU is finished with their operation,
我希望能把法哈德的遗体送回我国
I would like Farhad's remains to be returned to my country.
个人而言  我并不在乎他的尸首烂在何处
Personally, I don't care where his body rots,
但是我的母亲会希望他能得到厚葬
but my mother will want a proper burial.
这没有问题
I'll see that it's done.
但是  当前情况  总统阁下
But right now, Mr. President,
我们得疏散联合国总部大楼里的所有人
we need to evacuate the U.N.
我不会走的
I'm not leaving,
总统阁下  我要留下
Madame President. I'm staying here.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我女儿凯拉失踪了
My daughter Kayla is missing.
失踪了
Missing?
凯拉与我的前任安全主管有恋爱关系
Kayla is romantically involved with my former head of security.
她跟他私奔了
She's run off with him.
我能为您做些什么吗
Tell me what we can do to help.
我非常感激
I appreciate that,
不过我的侍卫队已经开始寻找她的下落
but my security teams are searching for her now.
我理解您有多么的担心
I understand how worried you must be,
但是即便你留下也帮不了她
but there is nothing that you can do to help her by staying here.
请你还是到一个安全的地方吧
Please come where you'll be safe.
我做不到  总统阁下
I can't, Madam President.
她一定还在城里某个地方
She's somewhere in the city,
她还不知道有核武器的威胁存在
with no idea that a nuclear threat exists.
在找到她之前我哪也不去
I won't go anywhere until she's been found.
好吧
All right.
我理解您的心情
I understand.
我会尽快和您再见面的
I will talk to you very soon.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们在第六大街向西转了
They're turning west at Sixth Street.
已经开进医院了
Pulling into the hospital.
克罗伊  把医院的监控画面调出来
Chloe, bring up the hospital security feed.
打开面部识别系统进行捕捉
Get facial recognition up and running.
面部识别系统运行中
Facial Recognition Filter Active
反恐组  我是鲍尔  我们正在前往预定地点
CTU, this is Bauer. We're moving into position.
法哈德的尸体已经被推到他的病房
Farhad's body's been taken to his room.
我们走
Let's go!
守住大门
Secure these doors!
切到外部监控画面上
Bring up the exterior cameras.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
杰克  是我
Jack, it's me.
我被释放了  可以走了
I've been released. I'm free to go.
很好
Good.
克罗伊告诉我你做的事了
Chloe told me what you did.
你和黑斯廷斯谈了条件
You leveraged Hastings.
你说这场危机化解之前
Said that you would head up field ops
你会一直指挥外勤行动
until this crisis was over
条件是反恐组撤销对我的所有指控
in exchange for CTU dropping any possible charges against me.
我没让你这么做  杰克
I didn't ask you to do that, Jack.
我知道你没有
I know you didn't.
白宫内部有人想陷害你
Look, someone in the White House is trying to set you up
把行动失败的责任全赖在你头上
to take responsibility for the failure of our mission,
我不能让他们得逞
and I couldn't let that happen
你什么错事都没做
because you did nothing wrong.
你能理解吗
You understand me?
蕾妮  你不要再纠结于这件事了
Renee, you need to let this go.
不管发生了什么  都不是你的责任
You're not responsible for what's happening.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
我先前说的话是认真的
Hey, I meant what I said earlier.
一切都平息之后  我会陪伴你左右
When this is over, I want to be there for you...
和你厮守在一起
with you.
-我很期待  -很好
- I'd like that. - Good.
我会派一个反恐组探员把你接到我的公寓
I'll have a CTU agent take you to my apartment.
事情结束之后  我去那里见你
I'll meet you there when this is over.
好的  杰克
All right, Jack.
有人在耳麦里呼我  我要挂了
Look, I'm getting chatter over the comm. I gotta go.
好  再见
Okay, bye.
我是鲍尔  请讲
This is Bauer. Go ahead.
杰克
Jack,
面部识别系统在伊斯兰共和国
facial recognition just picked up a match
情报人员文件中找到匹配结果了
with the I.R.K. Intelligence files.
他名叫马科斯·艾尔泽卡
His name's Marcos Al-Zacar.
在美国出生
American-born.
过去三年中为伊斯兰共和国从事间谍工作
Working undercover with the I.R.K. for the last three years.
他在哪
Where is he?
正在靠近侧门
Approaching the side entrance.
棕色头发  蓝色手术服  外面套着深蓝色夹克
Brown hair, blue scrubs, wearing a dark-blue jacket.
收到
Copy that.
等等  杰克  他手里有什么东西
Hold on, Jack. He's got something in his hand.
像是遥控引爆器
It looks like a remote detonator.
我想他身上绑有炸药
I think he's wearing a vest.
克罗伊  你能远程排爆吗
Chloe, can you disarm it from there?
也许吧  如果我能确认引爆器型号的话
Possibly, if I can pin down the detonator model,
我就可以用无线电发射器
I may be able to scramble the arming code
来扰乱引爆器发出的信号
using the transmitter in the mobile comm.
动手吧
Get on it.
欧文  有人正向你方靠近
Owen, you've got a man approaching your position.
他是棕色头发
He's got brown hair.
身穿蓝色手术服外面套着深蓝色夹克
He's wearing blue scrubs and a dark-blue jacket.
-我看见他了  -他就是杀手
- Yeah. I see him. - He's our hitter.
我们已确认他身着炸弹背心
We believe he's wearing an explosive vest
手持遥控引爆器
with a remote detonator.
好吧  我该怎么办
Okay. What should I do?
保持镇定  满足他的要求
Stay calm and do whatever he asks.
反恐组技术人员正尝试远程排爆
CTU techs are going to try and disarm the vest from offsite.
好的
Okay.
欧文
Owen?
Owen.
你可以做到的
You can do this.
只要尽可能拖住他就行了
Just try and slow him down as much as possible.
到处都有我们的人掩护你
We've got you covered every inch of the way.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
抱歉  这里是警戒区
Excuse me. This is a secure area.
请出示你的证件
I'm going to need to see some I.D.
仔细给我听好了
Listen to me very carefully.
我身上有炸弹
I have a bomb.
把你的武器给我  否则我们同归于尽
Give me your weapon right now, or I'll kill us both.
武器给我  快
Your weapon now.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
别激动
Just take it easy.
慢慢地
Slowly.
好
Yeah.
法哈德·哈桑在哪里
Where is Farhad Hassan?
在三楼
Third floor.
带我去找他
Take me to him.
有人问起我
Anyone asks who I am,
就说我是个医生  已通过安检
you say I'm a doctor, and I'm cleared.
加油  孩子
Come on, son.
好吧
Okay.
走吧
Move.
快点
Go.
喂
Hello?
达莉亚  是我
Dalia, it's me.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
别想让我改主意了  奥马
Don't try to change my mind, Omar.
我说过了  我去意已决
I told you, I'm leaving.
我打电话来不是为这事
I haven't called to change your mind.
凯拉或许有危险了
I called because Kayla may be in danger.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
她和塔林私奔了
She's run away with Tarin.
他们一直在一起交往
They've been seeing each other.
我知道
I know.
你知道多久了
How long have you known?
有关系吗  奥马
What difference does it make, Omar?
她有什么样的危险
What kind of danger is she in?
法哈德死了
Farhad is dead.
他曾想得到的核原料落到恐怖分子手里了
The nuclear material he tried to acquire is in the hands of the terrorists.
他们打算在曼哈顿就地使用
They're going to use it here in Manhattan.
不会吧
No.
到底怎么回事
How did this happen?
我以后再解释
I'll explain later.
但现在你得给凯拉打电话
But right now you need to call Kayla.
我留言了  但她不回我电话
I've left messages, but she won't return my calls.
但她也许会接你的电话
But she might talk to you.
拜托了  达莉亚  她很生我的气
Please, Dalia. She's angry at me.
我下令逮捕了塔林
I had Tarin arrested.
我当时以为他也是谋反者之一
I thought he was part of the conspiracy.
好吧
All right.
但奥马  你怎么办
But Omar, what about you?
别担心我了
Don't worry about me.
帮我找到女儿就行
Just help me find our daughter.
我尽力而为
I-I'll try.
塞碧拉  去找机长
Sabira, I need the captain.
克罗伊  我是杰克  我们正赶往三楼
Chloe, it's Jack. We're moving to the third floor.
排爆进行得怎么样了
Where are we at with the vest?
我已识别了引爆器型号  杰克
I've identified the detonator, Jack.
德国制造  型号K7
It's German-made, K7 variant,
但这个型号可用在多种结构的炸弹上
but that model is used in a lot of configurations.
我得看一眼那件炸弹背心
I'm going to need a visual on the vest.
收到
Copy that.
欧文  我是杰克
Owen, it's Jack.
反恐组得看到炸弹背心才能排爆
CTU cannot disarm the vest unless they see it.
我需要你把对方带到一个监视器下面
I need you to get the hostile underneath one of the surveillance cameras
让他给你看看炸弹
and make him show it to you.
重复一遍  反恐组得看到背心才能排爆
I repeat, CTU cannot disarm the vest unless they see it.
准备好了吗
You ready?
三队  他们正向你方靠近
Team three, they're approaching your position.
你想干什么
What are you doing?
我要看到证据
I want to see proof.
什么证据
Proof of what?
炸弹的
A bomb.
我不相信你有炸弹
I don't believe you have one.
你要是还不走  你就会知道我有没有了
You don't keep moving, you're gonna find out.
快点
Right now.
想找到法哈德  就给我看看
You want Farhad, you show me.
我叫你快走
I said, "Move."
不行
No.
欧文做到了  杰克  我看到背心了
Owen did it, Jack. I've got a visual on the vest.
-现在  走吧  -好
- Now, move. - Okay.
我们就在法哈德房间附近就位
We're set in position near Farhad's room.
现在情况怎么样了
Now, what's the status?
炸弹是德式构造
It's a DDR configuration.
我只需要找到接收器的频率
I just need to pull up the frequency of the receiver.
克罗伊  在他们到达房间之前
Chloe, you've got about 30 seconds
你还有三十秒钟
before they reach that room.
3.15千兆赫  全球通GSM标准
3.15 gigahertz, standard GSM.
正在无线电上运行
Running it through the mobile comm now.
得花上几秒钟
This'll take a few seconds.
准备出击
Stand by for assault.
趴下  脸朝下
On the floor, face down!
照我说的做
Do it now!
不许动
Don't move!
快点  阿洛
Come on, Arlo.
快点
Now.
好了  完成了
That's it. It's done.
杰克  排爆成功了
Jack, the vest is disarmed.
-冲进去  -行动
- Move in. - Go, go, go!
没事
It's all right.
没事的  放下你的武器
It's all right. Lower your weapons.
没事的
It's all right.
我把枪收起来
I'm going to put my gun away.
我们不会伤害你的
We're not here to hurt you.
我们只想谈谈
We just want to talk.
冷静
Stay calm.
没事的
It's all right.
我只是想跟你谈谈
I just want to talk to you.
不要
No. No!
他跑了  通知周围警力
He's still moving. Notify the perimeter.
别开火  他没武器
Do not fire! He's unarmed!
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
我在东区
I'm in the east wing.
嫌犯把自己反锁在某种压力舱内
Suspect has barricaded himself in some kind of pressure chamber.
我现在需要一个小组下来帮我把门打开
I need a team down here now to help me open the door.
怎么了
Yes?
这是个陷阱
It was a trap.
法哈德早就死了
Farhad was already dead.
-什么  -这是警方请君入瓮之计
- What? - The police were waiting.
他们想伏击我  不过我逃出来了
They tried to ambush me, but I got away.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我把自己反锁在某种氧气舱里了
I locked myself inside some kind of oxygen chamber.
他们进不来
They can't get in here.
起码现在还没进来
At least not yet.
你知道该做什么
You know what you must do.
不行
I can't.
我想他们干扰了引爆器信号
I-I think they-they scrambled the arming code.
你得手动引爆
You need to set it off manually.
我不知道怎么做
I don't know how to do that.
我教你
I'll talk you through it.
你能打开雷管的控制器吗
Can you open the detonator control?
是的  可以
Yeah. I-I think so.
得花上一分钟
Um, it's going to take a minute.
动作快点
Work quickly.
你不能让他们活捉你
You cannot let them take you alive.
能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
我只想谈谈
I just want to talk.